Guide to the Estela and Ernesto Bravo Film and Video Collection TAM.616
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Fidel: The Untold Story and Anecdotes about Fidel, 1995-2002; 477042
  - Bourne, Peter: Interview / Auction / Event for Elián González, 2000 November; 468043 (Box 2, Cassette ref10, Box 97, Dvd ref10)
    The bulk of this video features an interview with Peter Bourne. Bourne begins by speaking about the aftermath of the Cuban revolution specifically addressing the refugees and the trials of individuals connected to the Batista government. He also discusses Cuba's support of revolutions in Latin America, Castro's relationship with Maurice Bishop, the custody battle over Elián González, Cuban healthcare, Castro's views on globalization, and restrictions on freedom of speech. At minute 25:00 the video changes to footage of an auction featuring cigar boxes signed by Castro and dated March 3, 2000. At minute 27:35 footage changes to an event calling for the return of Elián González. The event features González's father Juan González Quintana, his grandmothers, and groups of school children performing Cuban songs and dances.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:35:54.
  - Campa, Concepción: Interview (part 1), circa 1995-2000; cuid307; 467999 (Box 3, Cassette ref54, Box 86, Dvd ref54)
    Concepción Campa Huergo (1951- ) is a pharmacist, biochemist, and lead scientist of the Cuban team that developed the meningitis B vaccine.
  - Campa, Concepción: Interview (part 2), circa 1995-2000; cuid308; 468000 (Box 3, Cassette ref53, Box 86, Dvd ref53)
  - Cardin, Pierre: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 477144 (Box 69, Cassette ref887, Box 85, Dvd ref887)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:21:03.
  - Cardin, Pierre/ Richard, Pierre: Interviews, 1996 March 13; cuid309; 468005 (Box 3, Cassette ref48, Box 86, Dvd ref48)
  - Castellanos, Baudilio: Interview, circa 1995-2000; cuid310; 479260 (Box 46, Cassette ref995, Box 95, Dvd ref995)
    Baudilio Castellanos Garcia ( -2002) was a lawyer and childhood friend of Fidel Castro. Castellanos attended law school with Castro, and served as one of the defense attorneys for captured insurgents arrested for the 1953 attack of the Moncada Barracks. Under the Castro government, Castellanos directed the National Institute of Tourism and served as Cuban Ambassador to France.
    In this portion of an interview with Baudillo Castellanos, Castellanos begins by speaking about his relationship with Fidel Castro prior to the revolution. He discusses Castro's first wife Mirta Díaz-Balart, and Castro's political activism prior to the revolution. The bulk of the interview focuses on Castellanos work representing Castro, and the other revolutionaries who were arrested after their attack on the Moncada Barracks. He discusses speaking with Díaz-Balart following the attack, and his legal representation of Raúl Castro prior to Fidel's capture. He also discusses the role of Marta Rojas who reported on the trials of the rebels captured at Moncada. At minute 22:44 Castellanos looks through photographs he saved from that period, and an image of Raúl Castro can be seen at the top of the stack. The video quality at the end of the recording is poor.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:30:34
  - Castellanos, Baudilio: Interview, circa 1995-2000; cuid311; 467975 (Box 2, Cassette ref78, Box 95, Dvd ref78)
  - Castellanos, Baudilio: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 477162 (Box 69, Cassette ref903, Box 85, Dvd ref903)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:21:51.
  - Castellanos, Baudilio: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 477163 (Box 69, Cassette ref904, Box 85, Dvd ref904)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:17:56.
  - Castellanos, Baudilio: Interview, circa 1995-2000; cuid312; 467963 (Box 2, Cassette ref90, Box 95, Dvd ref90)
  - Castellanos, Baudilio: Interview, circa 1995-2000; cuid313; 468009 (Box 3, Cassette ref44, Box 86, Dvd ref44)
  - Castro, Angela: Interview, 1995 October 22; cuid375; 479381 (Box 62, Cassette ref1042, Box 96, Dvd ref1042)
    Angela Castro was the sister of Cuban leader Fidel Castro.
    This video includes an interview with Angela Castro. In this brief portion of the interview, Castro discusses traveling to Santiago de Cuba during the revolution. She explains that her father was worried about her brothers after the attack on the Moncada Barracks, and sent her to Santiago de Cuba see if they were still alive. She describes her journey and the atmosphere of city when she arrived.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:10:35
  - Castro, Angela: Interview (part 1), circa 1995-2000; 467974 (Box 2, Cassette ref79, Box 97, Dvd ref79)
    Angela Maria Castro (1923-2012) was the eldest sister of Cuban revolutionary leaders Fidel and Raul Castro.
    This video features an informal discussion and brief interview with Angela Castro and one of her daughters. The beginning of the video features footage of Castro looking through family photographs and identifying individuals featured in the photos. The second half features an interview with Angela Castro's daughter. She discusses the revolutionary period and its impact on Castro's family, discussing her family's concern for Fidel and Raúl, specifically citing their imprisonment following the attack on the Moncada barracks and their exile in Mexico. She also discusses the isolation her family felt during the revolution and her memories of living with her grandparents in Birán during that time.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:31:24.
  - Castro, Angela: Interview (part 2), circa 1995-2000; cuid314; 467978 (Box 2, Cassette ref75, Box 95, Dvd ref75)
  - Castro, Angela: Interview (part 3), circa 1995-2000; 467977 (Box 2, Cassette ref76)
  - Castro, Angela: Interview (part 4), circa 1995-2000; 467968 (Box 2, Cassette ref85, Box 97, Dvd ref85)
    This interview with Angela Castro begins with a discussion about Alina Fernández Revuelta, Fidel Castro's eldest daughter. Castro contends that she does not believe Revuelta is her brother's daughter, but notes that he has never denied paternity. She also discusses her sister Juana Castro, who opposed her brother's politics and moved to the United States. Later in the interview Castro speaks about the impact the Cuban Revolution had on her life and her experience of having Fidel Castro as both a brother and a president. She also addresses criticism that her children received preferential treatment because Castro was their uncle.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:30:04.
  - Castro, Angela: Interview, with daughter Tania Frago -5, circa 1995-2000; cuid315; 467976 (Box 2, Cassette ref77, Box 95, Dvd ref77)
    Tania Frago Castro is the daughter of Angela Castro and a biotechnology specialist and an official in the Cuban Ministry of Health.
  - Castro, Angela: Interview, with daughter Tania Frago, circa 1995-2000; cuid316; 467962 (Box 2, Cassette ref91, Box 95, Dvd ref91)
  - Castro, Fidel: Interview on the Ed Sullivan Show, 1959 November 1; 467807 (Box 89, Cassette ref246, Box 77, Dvd ref246)
    Ed Sullivan traveled to Cuba to interview Fidel Castro immediately after his victory in the revolution. Sullivan compares Castro to George Washington and calls him a "gallant young leader."
    Original Format: Umatic. Duration: 00:11:49.
  - Clark, Ramsey: Interview, 1996 August 8; 477057 (Box 68, Cassette ref855, Box 84, Dvd ref855)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:10:49.
  - Clark, Ramsey: Interview, 1996 August 9; 477056 (Box 68, Cassette ref854, Box 84, Dvd ref854)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:27:24.
  - Clark, Ramsey: Photograph, undated; 592984 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Davis, Angela: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 477125 (Box 68, Cassette ref868, Box 84, Dvd ref868)
    Angela Davis talks about her experiences in Cuba and her feelings about Fidel Castro. She discusses Cuban Americans and her opposition to the US embargo.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:31:21.
  - Davis, Angela: Stills with Fidel, circa 1995-2000; cuid317; 468029 (Box 2, Cassette ref24, Box 86, Dvd ref24)
  - Depardieu, Gerard: Interview (part 1), circa 1995-2000; 467907 (Box 6, Cassette ref146, Box 97, Dvd ref146)
    This interview features French actor Gerard Depardieu. Depardieu discusses his impression of Fidel Castro as a leader, and talks about meeting him on three different occasions. He notes that he felt a close connection to Castro, and says that he saw a kinship between himself as an artist and Castro as a political revolutionary. Depardieu ends the interview by wishing Castro a happy 70th birthday, and speculates about what the future will be like for Castro and Cuba.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:20:01.
  - Espin, Vilma: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593341
    - Espin, Vilma: Interview Recording, circa 1995-2000; 467953 (Box 4, Cassette ref100, Box 76, Dvd ref100)
      Vilma Lucila Espin Guillois (1930-2007) was a Cuban revolutionary, feminist, and chemical engineer. She married Raul Castro in 1959, and later became President of the Federation of Cuban Women and a member of the Council of State of the Central Committee of the Cuban Communist Party. She was the most politically powerful woman in Cuba and for many years considered the country's unofficial first lady.
      Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:30:10.
    - Espin, Vilma: Interview Transcript, circa 1995-2000; 593342
  - Espin, Vilma: Interview Transcript, circa 1995-2000; 593343
    - Espin, Vilma: Interview Recording, circa 1995-2000; 467951 (Box 4, Cassette ref102, Box 76, Dvd ref102)
      Original Format: Betacam. Recording is divided into 2 access DVDs. Duration: Part 1 - 00:25:24; Part 2 - 00:03:26.
    - Espin, Vilma: Interview Transcript, circa 1995-2000; 593344
  - Espin, Vilma: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 467946 (Box 4, Cassette ref107, Box 76, Dvd ref107)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:29:09.
  - Espin, Vilma: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593345
    - Espin, Vilma: Interview Recording, circa 1995-2000; 467936 (Box 4, Cassette ref117, Box 76, Dvd ref117)
      Original Format: Betacam. Recording is divided into 2 access DVDs. Duration: Part 1 - 00:22:06; Part 2 - 00:08:55.
    - Espin, Vilma: Interview Transcript, circa 1995-2000; 593346
  - Esquivel, Chino: Interview, 1996 September 19; 477131 (Box 69, Cassette ref874, Box 84, Dvd ref874)
    Alfredo "El Chino" Esquivel Rodon (1926-2005) was a friend of Castro's at the University of Havana. He left Cuba for the US in 1964 but returned in 1992.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:30:03.
  - Esquivel, Chino: Interview, 1996 September 19; 477132 (Box 69, Cassette ref875, Box 84, Dvd ref875)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:31:15.
  - Esquivel, Chino: Interview, 1996 September 19; cuid318; 468026 (Box 2, Cassette ref27, Box 86, Dvd ref27)
  - Esquivel, Chino: Photographs, 1996 September 25; 468025 (Box 2, Cassette ref28, Box 97, Dvd ref28)
    This video features footage of still images of Fidel Castro and Alfredo "Chino" Esquivel. The images feature contemporary photographs of the two men shaking hands and greeting each other, and older photos of Castro and Esquivel as young men with their classmates from the University of Havana. This video does not contain any audio.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:20:36.
  - Fernandez, Conchita: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 477146 (Box 69, Cassette ref889, Box 85, Dvd ref889)
    Conchita Fernandez (1913-1998) was Fidel Castro's personal/executive secretary.
  - Fernandez, Conchita: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 477147 (Box 69, Cassette ref890, Box 85, Dvd ref890)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:23:51.
  - Fernandez, Conchita: Interview, circa 1995-2000; cuid405; 468010 (Box 3, Cassette ref43, Box 86, Dvd ref43)
  - Fernandez, Jose Ramon: Interview -1, circa 1995-2000; 477154 (Box 69, Cassette ref897, Box 85, Dvd ref897)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:29:13.
  - Fernandez, Jose Ramon: Interview -3, circa 1995-2000; 477155 (Box 69, Cassette ref898, Box 85, Dvd ref898)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:05:51.
  - Fernandez, Jose Ramon: Interview, circa 1995-2000; cuid406; 468014 (Box 3, Cassette ref39, Box 86, Dvd ref39)
  - Frady, Marshall: Interview, 1996 September 9; 477126 (Box 68, Cassette ref869, Box 84, Dvd ref869)
    In this interview Estela Bravo asks Marshall Frady about people's criticism of Fidel Castro for human rights abuses in Cuba. Frady argues that many of the negative reactions against Castro were formed during the Cold War, and that much of the antipathy directed at Castro formed as a result of decades of poor diplomatic relations between Cuba and the United States. The bulk of the interview focuses on popular perceptions of Fidel Castro, in which Frady describes him as a figure that inspired passionate reactions, both positive and negative. The interview is in English.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:30:37.
  - Frady, Marshall: Interview, 1996 September 9; 593347
    - Frady, Marshall: Interview Recording, 1996 September 9; 468024 (Box 4, Cassette ref29, Box 75, Dvd ref29)
    - Frady, Marshall: Interview Transcript, 1996 September 9; 593348
  - Frady, Marshall: Interview, 1996; 468022 (Box 4, Cassette ref31, Box 75, Dvd ref31)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:29:02.
  - Fusté, Tomás García: Interview (part 1), circa 1995-2000; 477176 (Box 70, Cassette ref917, Box 85, Dvd ref917)
    Tomas Garcia Fuste is an anti-Castro radio and television talk show host. He was part of the first wave of voluntary exiles from Cuba after the revolution, arriving in Miami in 1960.
    The initial six minutes consists of background footage of the WQBA-La Cubanisima radio building, where the interview was conducted.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:30:12.
  - Fusté, Tomás García: Interview (part 2), circa 1995-2000; 479316 (Box 46, Cassette ref1000, Box 97, Dvd ref1000)
    This video features an interview with Miami radio host Tomás García Fusté. The video begins with footage of images in Fusté's office and an interview that starts at minute 5:30. Fusté begins by speculating about end of the Castro presidency, which he predicts will occur within a year of the time in which the interview was conducted. He also talks about his family members still living in Cuba, and the state of the country. He discusses Cuban exiles who have attempted to reach the US by raft or in the Mariel Boatlift, and blames Castro for the tragedies that had have happened as a result of people fleeing the country. Finally, Fusté discusses other anti-Castro Cubans in the United States including Orlando Bosch and Jorge Mas Canosa.
  - Gades, Antonio: Interview, 1996 August 7; 477145 (Box 69, Cassette ref888, Box 85, Dvd ref888)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:21:44.
  - Garcia, Juanita Vera: Interview, circa 1995-2000; cuid319; 467840 (Box 10, Cassette ref213)
    Juanita Vera Garcia was Fidel Castro's official translator. She has also worked as the official translator for Raul Castro.
  - Garcia, Juanita Vera: Interview "2 Tape B", circa 1995-2000; cuid320; 467834 (Box 10, Cassette ref219)
  - Gonzalez, Elián (and his lawyer), 2000; 477133 (Box 69, Cassette ref876, Box 84, Box ref876)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:31:50.
  - González, Elián CNN footage, circa 2000; 479373 (Box 62, Cassette ref1034)
  - González, Elián- "extracts from VHS", circa 2000; 467827 (Box 10, Cassette ref226, Box 97, Dvd ref226)
    This video features footage of Elián González in Cuba. The video begins with extended footage of González arriving in Cuba with his father. As he and his father depart from the plane they are greeted by large crowds and a group of relatives including González's grandparents. The video then cuts to footage of crowds lining the street as González rides home. The video also features footage of Elián González at the beach with his family, going to school, and ends with footage of him reading La Edad de Oro by José Martí, which was a gift from Fidel Castro.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:23:32.
  - González, Elián "Comp Reel", circa 2000; 467832 (Box 10, Cassette ref221)
  - González (Quintana), Juan Miguel: Interview, 2000 November; 477043 (Box 68, Cassette ref844, Box 83, Dvd ref844)
    Juan Miguel González Quintana is the father of Elián González.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:31:35.
  - González (Quintana), Juan Miguel: Interview, continuation, 2000 November; 477047 (Box 68, Cassette ref845, Box 83, Dvd ref845)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:22:40.
  - González (Quintana), Juan Miguel: Interview 1, 2000; 479392 (Box 62, Cassette ref1053)
  - González (Quintana), Juan Miguel: Interview 2, 2000; 479394 (Box 62, Cassette ref1055)
  - González (Quintana), Juan Miguel: Interview 3, 2000; 479393 (Box 62, Cassette ref1054)
  - González (Quintana), Juan Miguel: Interview, 2000; 467841 (Box 10, Cassette ref212)
  - González Corrales, Manuel: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 467973 (Box 2, Cassette ref80, Box 97, Dvd ref80)
    Manuel González Corrales (1916-2014) was a friend of Fidel Castro at the University of Havana.
    This video begins with a brief discussion with one of Fidel Castro's university classmates about a 1980 reunion between Castro and his friends from the University of Havana. The brief footage focuses on a photograph from the event. At minute 3:35 the video changes to an interview with Manuel González Corrales. He discusses his memories of Fidel Castro at the University of Havana and their shared involvement in student activism. He describes the political environment within the university as a microcosm and training ground for the revolutionary movements that developed in Cuba, and later discusses the assassination of Student Federation leader Manolo Castro.
  - "González, Manuel Corrales Cassette #47", circa 1995-2000; 479261 (Box 46, Cassette ref996)
  - Guevara, Alfredo: Interview (part 1), 1996 May 27; 477166 (Box 70, Cassette ref907, Box 85, Dvd ref907)
    Alfredo Guevara Valdes (1925-2013) was a lifelong friend of Fidel Castro. They were students at the University of Havana, where Guevara was a member of the Communist Youth organization. After the Cuban revolution, Guevara became vice minister of Culture and established the Cuban Institute for Arts and Cinematography (I.C.A.I.C.), which sponsored Cuba's state-funded cinema. After leaving the ICAIC 1982, he spent nine years as Cuban ambassador to the United Nations educational, scientific and cultural organization (UNESCO).
  - Guevara, Alfredo: Interview (part 2), 1996 May 27; 479262 (Box 94, Cassette ref997, Box 86, Dvd ref997)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:26:22.
  - Guevara, Aleida: Interview (part 1), 1996; cuid322; 479403 (Box 63, Cassette ref1064, Box 96, Dvd ref1064)
    Aleida Guevara March (1960- ) is the eldest daughter of four children born to Ernesto "Che" Guevara and his second wife, Aleida March. A medical doctor, Guevara is based at the William Soler Children's Hospital in Havana and has also worked as a physician in Angola, Ecuador, and Nicaragua.
    In this interview Aleida Guevara begins with a discussion about her earliest memories of Fidel Castro. She then discusses Castro asking her to write a prolog for a book about her father, Ernesto "Che" Guevara, and his role supporting the unsuccessful revolution in Congo. She describes her enjoyment writing the prolog because it allowed her to revisit positive memories of her father. She also describes Castro's relationship with Guevara, and how Castro convinced him to return to Cuba briefly before he left to support guerilla forces in Bolivia. In the last half of the interview, she reads from the letter Castro wrote to her father convincing him to return to Cuba.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:23:28.
  - Guevara, Aleida: Interview (part 1), 1998 June 21; cuid324; 480306 (Box 3, Cassette ref1396, Box 95, Dvd ref1396)
  - Guevara, Aleida: Interview (part 2), 1998 June 21; cuid325; 467982 (Box 3, Cassette ref71, Box 95, Dvd ref71)
  - Guevara, Aleida: Interview (part 3), 1998 June 21; cuid326; 467989 (Box 3, Cassette ref64, Box 86, Dvd ref64)
  - Guevara, Aleida: Interview (part 4), 1998 June 21; cuid327; 467986 (Box 3, Cassette ref67, Box 95, Dvd ref67)
  - Haines, Randa: Interview, 1996 November 9; 477130 (Box 68, Cassette ref873, Box 84, Dvd ref873)
    Randa Haines (1945- ) is a film and television director and producer, most famous for directing the film Children of a Lesser God.
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:16:50.
  - Heath, Edward: Interview, 1996 March 15; cuid328; 468002 (Box 4, Cassette ref51, Box 76, Dvd ref51)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:24:23.
  - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 477164 (Box 69, Cassette ref905, Box 85, Dvd ref905)
    Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:31:41.
  - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593349
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 467980 (Box 4, Cassette ref73, Box 76, Dvd ref73)
      Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:30:01.
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593350
  - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593351
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 467972 (Box 4, Cassette ref81, Box 76, Dvd ref81)
      Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:26:55.
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593352
  - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593353
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 467970 (Box 4, Cassette ref83, Box 76, Dvd ref83)
      Original Format: Betacam. Recording is divided into 2 access DVDs. Duration: Part 1 - 00:16:31; Part 2 - 00:12:54.
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593354
  - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593355
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 467964 (Box 4, Cassette ref89, Box 76, Dvd ref89)
      Original Format: Betacam. Recording is divided into 4 access DVDs. Duration: Part 1 - 00:15:11; Part 2 - 00:01:50; Part 3 - 00:00:43; Part 4 - 00:11:41.
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593356
  - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593357
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 467956 (Box 76, Dvd ref97, Box 4, Cassette ref97)
      Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:29:26.
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview, circa 1995-2000; 593358
  - Hernández, Melba: Interview with Ana Fidelia, circa 1995-2000; 593359
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview with Ana Fidelia, circa 1995-2000; 467940 (Box 4, Cassette ref113, Box 76, Dvd ref113)
      Original Format: Betacam. Recording is divided into 4 access DVDs. Duration: Part 1 - 00:05:26; Part 2 - 00:02:35; Part 3 - 00:01:20, Part 4 - 00:01:20.
    - Hernández, Melba: Interview with Ana Fidelia, circa 1995-2000; 593360
  - Interview List, undated; 590723 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Interview Transcripts, 1996; 590726 (Box 72, Folder 7-12)
  - Jackson, Jesse: Interview, 1996 September 17; cuid329; 468020 (Box 2, Cassette ref33, Box 86, Dvd ref33)
  - Jiménez, Antonio Núñez: Interview (with stills), 1996; 593361
    - Jiménez, Antonio Núñez: Interview Recording (with stills), 1996; 477148 (Box 69, Cassette ref891, Box 85, Dvd ref891)
      Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:21:52.
    - Jiménez, Antonio Núñez: Interview Transcript, 1996; 593362
  - Jiménez, Antonio Núñez: Interview, 1996; 593363
    - Jiménez, Antonio Núñez: Interview Recording, 1996; 468003 (Box 4, Cassette ref50, Box 76, Dvd ref50)
      Original Format: Betacam. Duration: 00:30:43.
    - Jiménez, Antonio Núñez: Interview Transcript, 1996; 593364
  - Jiménez, Antonio Núñez: Interview, 1996; 593365
    - Jiménez, Antonio Núñez: Interview Recording, 1996; 467945; 4 items 3 access CDs and 1 video cassette (Box 4, Cassette ref108, Box 76, Dvd ref108)